Guide to the Bob Holman Audio/Video Poetry Collection 1977-2002 MSS.128
Fales Library and Special Collections
Series XI: Miscellaneous Video consists of seventy-four videotapes in the form of VHS and 3/4 inch Umatic cassettes along with two reels of 16mm film. The Umatics in this series may be of unique content and possibly of superior quality. While some of the series' contents are commercially released tapes, most are believed to be dubs. Among their contents are recordings of works by poets Maggie Estep, Sekou Sundiata, Allen Ginsberg, and Bill Moyers. The two 16mm film reels are recordings of elementary education films regarding poetry and haikus.
Series XII: Vinyl Sound Recordings contains a substantial quantity of vinyl long play records. Their arangement reflects Bob Holman's original order. The vast majority of these are commercial releases but there is also a small number of test pressings. The series is arranged into five subseries:
Subseries A: Vinyl Recordings - LPs 12in. and Subseries B: Vinyl Recordings EPs 7in., are composed primarily of spoken word recordings, particularly rap and poetry. They also include some rock and roll and recorded dramas.
Subseries C: Vinyl Recordings - African American consists of recordings of spoken word and musical performances from African American artists, including readings of the poetry of Imamu Amiri Baraka and Linton Kwesi Johnson and performances by The Last Poets.
Subseries D: Vinyl Recordings - Various Poets contains spoken word performances from a variety of poets and, to a lesser extent, comedians such as Lord Buckley.
Subseries E: Vinyl Recordings - Allen Ginsberg is composed of a collection of spoken word and musical recordings previousky owned by Allen Ginsberg, which Holman purchased at a Sotheby's auction in October of 1999.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Access copies for audiovisual materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Sound recordings.; Poets, American -- 20th century.; Poets -- United States.; Poetry -- 20th century.; Poetry, Modern |y 20th century.; Mini-DV.; Betacam-SP.; Super-VHS (TM); VHS; Poets.; Poetry -- Study and teaching.; Betacam (TM); United States of Poetry (Television Program); Audiocassettes.; Poetry -- Competitions.; Progressive rock music.; Poetry slams.; Art, American -- New York (State) -- 20th century.; American poetry -- 20th century -- History and criticism.; Experimental theater -- New York (State) -- New York.; American poetry -- 20th century.; Record covers.; Videotapes.; Avant-garde poetry.; Audiovisual materials.; Poetry.; New York (N.Y.); Videocassettes.; Moving images.; Magnetic tapes.; Long-playing records.; Rap (Music); Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.); Film (material by form); Avant-garde (Music); 16mm; Rap (Music)|x History and criticism.; Video recordings.; Dial-a-Poem Poets; Last Poets (Group); Fugs (Musical group); Firesign Theatre (Performing group); Finley, Karen; Roxanne Shanté, 1969-; Johnson, Linton Kwesi, 1952-; Ginsberg, Allen, 1926-1997; Anderson, Laurie, 1947-; Run-D.M.C. (Musical group); Baraka, Amiri, 1934-2014; Beastie Boys; Lord Buckley; Estep, Maggie; Cohen, Leonard, 1934-; D.J. Jazzy Jeff; Fresh Prince; LL Cool J, 1968-; Torres, Edwin, 1965-; Grandmaster Flash; Captain Beefheart; Sundiata, Sekou; Mouth Almighty/Mercury Records
- Series I: Spoken Word Tapes of/ Produced by Bob Holman, 1977-1994
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Laudromat Part 1, 1977 (Media ID: 128.0813)
      General
      Format: VHS
    - Laudromat Part 2, 1977 (Media ID: 128.0816)
    - Clear the Range, 1977 (Media ID: 128.0819)
    - Bob Holman: Panic DJ 11/8/80, 1980 (Media ID: 128.0936)
      General Note
      Format: DVD
      Duration: 01:03:00
    - Niteline/Poetry Show History 6.18.92, 1992 (Media ID: 128.0948)
      Duration: 00:30:30
    - Rap Meets Poetry, 1993 Raw Footage 1 (Media ID: 128.0972)
      Duration: 01:00:00
    - Rap Meets Poetry, 1993 Raw Footage 4 (Media ID: 128.0978)
      Duration: 00:58:00
    - Rap Meets Poetry - Raw Footage 1993 #6 (Media ID: 128.0957)
      Duration: 00:56:00
    - Rap Meets Poetry 8, Undated (Media ID: 128.0960)
      Duration: 00:23:00
    - Rap Meet Poetry, 1993 Raw Footage Tape 8 (tape 6 on the container) (Media ID: 128.0975)
      Duration: 00:59:00
    - From City Arts Show #103 "New Year in Verse", Undated (Media ID: 128.0969)
      Duration: 00:32:30
    - Bob Holman Audio Channel #1, Undated (Media ID: 128.0939)
      Duration: 00:20:00
    - Bob Holman - 10 Minutes of Panic, Undated (Media ID: 128.0942)
      Duration: 00:22:30
    - Holman Compiled Pass 1, Undated (Media ID: 128.0951)
      Duration: 00:10:00
    - Poetry Demo Master, Undated (Media ID: 128.0981)
      Duration: 00:04:00
    - Poet's Demo Reel - NU.YO. NUYO Records Video Presentation, Undated (Media ID: 128.0963)
    - Tape 2 Raw Footage - Poets, Undated (Media ID: 128.0966)
      Duration: 00:23:30
    - Teaching, Undated (Media ID: 128.0945)
      Duration: 00:09:30
    - Words in Your Face RT: 28 min., Undated (Media ID: 128.0954)
      Duration: 00:28:00
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Laundromat 1, 1977; ID: 128.0001 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0001)
      Format: 1/2 in. Open
    - Laundromat 1, 1977; ID: 128.0002 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0002)
    - Laundromat 2, 1977; ID: 128.0003 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0003)
    - Laundromat 2, 1977; ID: 128.0004 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0004)
    - Clear the Range, 1977; ID: 128.0005 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0005)
    - Rapp It Up! Poets In Performance, Undated; ID: 128.0006 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0006)
    - PTV: Ginsberg, Waldman, Holman, Undated; ID: 128.0007 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0007)
    - Ginsberg, Waldman, Holman, Undated; ID: 128.0008 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0008)
    - Poets [Theater] Festival 1, 1988; ID: 128.0009 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0009)
    - Poets [Theater] Festival 2, [1988]; ID: 128.0010 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0010)
    - Head to the Future 5/20/89, 1989; ID: 128.0011 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0011)
    - Head to the Future 5/20, 21/89, 1989; ID: 128.0012 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0012)
    - Head to the Future 5/21/89, 1989; ID: 128.0013 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0013)
    - Poets Theater Tape 1, 1990; ID: 128.0014 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0014)
    - Poets Theater Tape 2, 1990; ID: 128.0015 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0015)
    - Poets Theater Tape 2, 1990; ID: 128.0016 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0016)
    - Return To The Future 1990 II, ID: 128.0017 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0017)
    - Return To The Future 1990 III A, ID: 128.0018 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0018)
    - Return To The Future 1990 III B, ID: 128.0019 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0019)
    - Return To The Future 1990; Xtra: Father Pedro, Avon, ID: 128.0020 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0020)
    - Sunday Tape #3 - Panasonic Camera, 1986; ID: 128.0021 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0021)
    - Saturday and Sunday Tape #2 - Panasonic Camera, 1986; ID: 128.0022 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0022)
    - Sunday Tape #3 - Minolta Camera, 1986; ID: 128.0023 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0023)
    - Saturday Tape #1 Brooklyn - Minolta Camera, 1986; ID: 128.0024 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0024)
    - Saturday and Sunday Tape #2 - Minolta Camera, 1986; ID: 128.0025 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0025)
    - Saturday Tape #1 Brooklyn - Panasonic Camera, 1986; ID: 128.0026 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0026)
    - Double Talk @ Los Amigos, 1988; ID: 128.0027 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0027)
    - Double Talk Show, [1985]; ID: 128.0028 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0028)
    - Bob Holman & Pedro Pietri, 1987; ID: 128.0029 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0029)
    - Pre-Resurrection Insurrection, 1987; ID: 128.0030 (Box 1, Media ID: 128.0030)
    - Poets In The Bars Reading #3, 1989; ID: 128.0031 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0031)
      Format: S-VHS
    - Poets In The Bars #1, 1989; ID: 128.0032 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0032)
    - Poets In The Bars #5, 1989; ID: 128.0033 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0033)
    - Poets In The Bars # 6, 1989; ID: 128.0034 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0034)
    - Poets In The Bars #7, 1989; ID: 128.0035 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0035)
    - Poets In The Bars #8, 1989; ID: 128.0036 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0036)
    - Poets In The Bars #8, 1989; ID: 128.0037 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0037)
    - Not Another Poetry Reading I, 1984; ID: 128.0038A (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0038A)
    - Not Another Poetry Reading II, 1984; ID: 128.0039 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0039)
    - The Poetrey Project: Pedro Pietri, Undated; ID: 128.0040 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0040)
    - Rap It Up!, Undated; ID: 128.0041 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0041)
    - Bob Holman: Panic DJ, 1980; ID: 128.0042 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0042)
      Format: 3/4 in. Umatic
    - Bob Holman; Audio Channel #1, Undated; ID: 128.0043 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0043)
    - Bob Holman: Ten Minutes of Panic, Undated; ID: 128.0044 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0044)
    - 5 Minutes of Panic, Undated; ID: 128.0045 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0045)
    - 5 minutes of Panic*DJ!, Undated; ID: 128.0046 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0046)
    - "We Interrupt…", The Meaning of Meaning, Hey, What'd I Say, Undated; ID: 128.0047 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0047)
    - Rapp It Up! "Meaning of Meaning" Live from The Double Talk Show, Undated; ID: 128.0048 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0048)
    - Television Is Not A Box, Undated; ID: 128.0049 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0049)
    - Panic*DJ!, 1989; ID: 128.0050 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0050)
    - Jamestown Bob, Undated; ID: 128.0051 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0051)
    - Poet In The 3rd Dimension, Jamestown, 1990; ID: 128.0052 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0052)
    - Poet In The 3rd Dimension - short version, Undated; ID: 128.0053 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0053)
    - North Country Nightly, 1989; ID: 128.0054 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0054)
    - Bob Holman Teaching, Undated; ID: 128.0055 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0055)
    - Forien Eyes; Panic/DJ; Jason Heact, Undated; ID: 128.0056 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0056)
    - Teaching, Undated; ID: 128.0057 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0057)
    - PLVP - Long Version; Best Talk In Town, Undated; ID: 128.0058 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0058)
    - Rooms Of Our Lives, Undated; ID: 128.0059 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0059)
    - Panic DJ!, Undated; ID: 128.0060 (Box 2, Media ID: 128.0060)
    - Panic DJ!, Undated; ID: 128.0061 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0061)
    - Panic DJ!, Undated; ID: 128.0062 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0062)
    - Panic DJ!, Undated; ID: 128.0063 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0063)
    - Huge Voodoo Improv., 1992; ID: 128.0064 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0064)
    - [1]-- Aluminum Assemble Reel [2]-- Global Assembly Line, Undated; ID: 128.0065 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0065)
    - [1]-- Border Crossings Sample [2]-- Host/Narrator Selects [3]-- Around the World With Ford, Undated; ID: 128.0066 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0066)
    - Multinational Tapes: Hoover Vacuums, Coca-cola, Beatrice Foods, A&P Coffee, General Motors, Undated; ID: 128.0067 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0067)
    - Aluminum on the March - Sample Reel, Undated; ID: 128.0068 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0068)
    - Niteline/ Poetry Show History, 1992; ID: 128.0069 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0069)
    - Holman Compiled 92, [1992]; ID: 128.0070 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0070)
    - Charlie Rose Show, 1992; ID: 128.0071 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0071)
    - Charlie Rose, 1992; ID: 128.0072 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0072)
    - Good Morning America, Undated; ID: 128.0073 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0073)
    - ABC News Magazine, Undated; ID: 128.0074 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0074)
    - Nightline: Poetry In America, 1992; ID: 128.0075 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0075)
    - New Poetry on TV, 1992; ID: 128.0076 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0076)
    - New Poetry on TV, 1992; ID: 128.0077 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0077)
    - Charlie Rose, 1992; ID: 128.0078 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0078)
    - Dark Star Crew at Poets Cafe, 1990; ID: 128.0079 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0079)
    - Heart of the City, Undated; ID: 128.0080 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0080)
    - MTV Pass One: UR-"Smokin' Word", Undated; ID: 128.0081 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0081)
    - Arty Party, Undated; ID: 128.0082 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0082)
    - Words In Your Face - Rough Cut, 1991; ID: 128.0083 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0083)
    - Words Face WETV, 1991; ID: 128.0084 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0084)
    - Words In Your Face, 1991; ID: 128.0085 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0085)
    - Words In Your Face, 1991; ID: 128.0086 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0086)
    - Words In Your Face, 1991; ID: 128.0087 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0087)
    - Words In Your Face, 1991; ID: 128.0088 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0088)
    - Words In Your Face, 1991; ID: 128.0089 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0089)
    - Words In Your Face, 1991; ID: 128.0090 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0090)
    - Words In Your Face, [1991]; ID: 128.0091 (Box 3, Media ID: 128.0091)
    - MoMA; Between Word and Image, Undated; ID: 128.0092 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0092)
    - Nuyorican's Poet's Café; Popularly Poetic, Undated; ID: 128.0093A (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0093A)
    - Holman Compiled Pass 1 & Charlie Rose, Undated; ID: 128.0094 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0094)
      Format: Betacam
    - Bob Holman 2, Undated; ID: 128.0095 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0095)
    - Bob Holman 2, Undated; ID: 128.0096 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0096)
    - Spoken Word Unplugged, [1993]; ID: 128.0097A (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0097A)
    - MTV Unplugged Spoken Word Air Tape, 1993; ID: 128.0098 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0098)
    - The United States of Poetry Supplement - Sample Reel, Undated; ID: 128.0099 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0099)
    - Heckler's Slam: Connie Chung, Undated; ID: 128.0100 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0100)
    - Pamela Sneed-Excerpt from Smoki' Word, Undated; ID: 128.0101 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0101)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Raw Footage #6, 1993; ID: 128.0102 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0102)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Raw Footage #8, 1993; ID: 128.0103 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0103)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Nuyo Records Video Presentation, [1993]; ID: 128.0104 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0104)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Raw Footage #2, 1993; ID: 128.0105 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0105)
    - Word Up, [1994]; ID: 128.0106 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0106)
    - Word Up, [1994]; ID: 128.0107 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0107)
    - Word Up, [1994]; ID: 128.0108 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0108)
    - Word Up, [1994]; ID: 128.0109 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0109)
    - Poetry Resurgence, 1994; ID: 128.0110 (Box 4, Media ID: 128.0110)
    - Sinovision; Poetry Slam 95, 1995; ID: 128.0111 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0111)
    - Nuyorican Poets Café Live - SAMPLER, 1994; ID: 128.0112 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0112)
    - Nuyoricans Poets BBC Late Show 2nd Cut, 1995; ID: 128.0113 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0113)
    - Nuyoricans Poets BBC Late Show 2nd Cut, 1995; ID: 128.0114 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0114)
    - Nuyoricans Poets BBC Late Show 2nd Cut, 1995; ID: 128.0115 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0115)
    - Action Poetry '94, 1994; ID: 128.0116A (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0116A)
    - "I'd Rather Be Thin Than Famous" - Writers On Kerouac, Undated; ID: 128.0117 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0117)
    - From City Arts Show #103 "New York In Verse", 1995; ID: 128.0118 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0118)
    - City Arts; New York In Verse - Show #103, 1995; ID: 128.0119 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0119)
    - "United States Of Poetry" [1]-- MTV News [2]-- WWOR-TV News, 1996; ID: 128.0120 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0120)
    - Bucher, Bucher, 1997; ID: 128.0121 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0121)
    - Slammin', Undated; ID: 128.0122 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0122)
    - Slammin', Undated; ID: 128.0123 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0123)
    - Slamnation Partial Rough Cut, Undated; ID: 128.0124 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0124)
    - Slam Nation - The Sport of Spoken Word, Undated; ID: 128.0125 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0125)
    - National Poetry Slam Demo, [1996]; ID: 128.0126 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0126)
    - "U.S. of Poetry"; Last Word #65, 1996; ID: 128.0127 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0127)
    - Bob Holman (1), Undated; ID: 128.0128 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0128)
    - Bob Holman, Undated; ID: 128.0129 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0129)
    - Poetry By Numbers, Undated; ID: 128.0130 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0130)
    - Clear the Range, Undated; ID: 128.0131 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0131)
    - Scene and Heard, 1996; ID: 128.0132 (Box 5, Media ID: 128.0132)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Raw Footage #3, 1993; ID: 128.0133 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0133)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Raw Footage #1, 1993; ID: 128.0134 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0134)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Raw Footage #6, 1993; ID: 128.0135 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0135)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Raw Footage #7, 1993; ID: 128.0136 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0136)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Raw Footage #4, 1993; ID: 128.0137 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0137)
    - Rap Meets Poetry Demo Master, 1993; ID: 128.0138 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0138)
    - Flippin' The Script - Tape #1, 1995; ID: 128.0139 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0139)
      Format: Hi 8 mm
    - Flippin' The Script - Tape #2, 1995; ID: 128.0140 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0140)
    - Flippin' The Script at "SOBS'" Tape #1, 1996; ID: 128.0141 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0141)
    - Flippin' The Script at "SOBS'" Tape #2, 1996; ID: 128.0142 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0142)
    - Flippin' The Script at "SOBS'" Tape #3, 1996; ID: 128.0143 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0143)
    - Flippin' The Script …Rap Meets Poetry, 1994; ID: 128.0144 (Box 6, Media ID: 128.0144)
- Series II: WNYC-TV "Poetry Spots", 1985-1992
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III, Tape 1, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0822)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III, Tape 2, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0825)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III, Tape 3, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0828)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III, Tape 4, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0831)
    - The Law is the Seed - Billy Two Rivers, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0834)
    - The Law is the Seed - Final Edit Withour Credits, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0837)
    - The Law is the Seed - Final Edit With Credits, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0840)
    - Just Another Day - Tape #1, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0843)
    - Just Another Day - Tape #2, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0846)
    - Unwilling Suspension by John Ash, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0849)
    - You Startin' Wif Me; a poem by Tracie Morris, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0852)
    - "Nostalgia"; Laura Ciporen, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0855)
    - Bacalaitos y Fireworks by Lois Griffith, 1992 (Media ID: 128.0858)
    - A Child's Guide to Parenthood; Laura Ciporen, [1991] (Media ID: 128.0861)
    - Treadwinds; Walter K. Lew, [1994] (Media ID: 128.0864)
    - Just Another Day; Sandy Esteves 1/31/1992 (Media ID: 128.0867)
    - The Law is the Seed - Alex Jacobs Interview - Raw Footage, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0870)
    - "Charlie" - Short Version, 1991 (Media ID: 128.0873)
    - [Poetry Spot Season II Intro and Credits], 1991 (Media ID: 128.0876)
    - [Poetry Spot Season III Intro], 1993 (Media ID: 128.0879)
    - [1.]--Another Poem About UFOs [2.]-- Rapunzel Was A Sister… [3.]-- Oil Glut Sensaround, Undated (Media ID: 128.0882)
    - [Poetry Spots Season V Intro and Credits], Undated (Media ID: 128.0885)
    - [Arlene Gottfried 1991 Shoot; El Barrio - Tape 1] (Media ID: 128.0888)
    - [Arlene Gottfried 1991 Shoot; El Barrio - Tape 2] (Media ID: 128.0891)
    - [Monologues of an Anonymogamist - Raw Footage Tape 1], 1989 (Media ID: 128.0894)
    - [Monologues of an Anonymogamist - Raw Footage Tape 2], 1989 (Media ID: 128.0897)
    - [Nuyorican Poets Café - Rough Cut], 1990 (Media ID: 128.0900)
    - Transformations; Poems of Change, 1995 (Media ID: 128.0903)
    - [Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel, Season I], [1990] (Media ID: 128.0906)
    - [Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel; Season Two. Part I], 1991 (Media ID: 128.0909)
    - [Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel; Season Two. Part II], 1991 (Media ID: 128.0912)
    - [Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel; Season III], 1992 (Media ID: 128.0915)
    - [Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel; Season IV], 1993 (Media ID: 128.0918)
    - Poetry Spots 4 Compilation Reel, 1993 (Media ID: 128.0921)
    - Poetry Spots Five - Compilation Reel, 1994 (Media ID: 128.0924)
    - Poetry Spots Five - Compilation Reel, 1994 (Media ID: 128.0927)
    - Latin Empire - Dub Master B Roll, [1991] (Media ID: 128.0930)
    - Latin Empire - Dub Master B Roll With Timecode, [1991] (Media ID: 128.0933)
    - The Great American Roller Coaster Poem - Final Edit, undated (Media ID: 128.1008)
      Duration: [00:05:00]
      Original Format: VHS T-15
    - Video Poetry: Deaf Poets Tape 2A, 1989 (Media ID: 128.1011)
      Duration: [00:10:00]
      Original Format: Betacam
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Y Can't We Be Friends?, Undated; ID: 128.0145 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0145)
    - Why Can't We Be Friends? - Latin Empire, Undated; ID: 128.0146 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0146)
    - Latin Empire, Undated; ID: 128.0147 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0147)
    - Why Can't We Be Friends? - Latin Empire, Undated; ID: 128.0148 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0148)
    - Latin Empire - 2nd Roll, Undated; ID: 128.0149 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0149)
    - Latin Empire 3rd Tape, Undated; ID: 128.0150 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0150)
    - Show #1 Tape #4, 1989; ID: 128.0151 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0151)
    - Poetry Videos: Nancy Mercado "Jazz 101", 1989; ID: 128.0152 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0152)
    - Poetry Videos: Nancy Mercado "Holding Up Walls", 1989; ID: 128.0153 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0153)
    - Poetry Videos Tape 10: Nancy Mercado, 1989; ID: 128.0154A (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0154A)
    - Poetry Videos Tape #15; Yehuda Amachai, 1989; ID: 128.0155A (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0155A)
    - Poetry Slam, Undated; ID: 128.0156 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0156)
    - [1]-- Edit master Pozmade del City [2]--Edit Master #2 [3]-- More In Than Out [3]-- NTOZAKE, Undated; ID: 128.0157 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0157)
    - Paul Beatty Shoot #1, Undated; ID: 128.0158 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0158)
    - P.S. The Law Is In The Seed, Undated; ID: 128.0159 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0159)
    - John Ash Poem (PSII), Undated; ID: 128.0160 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0160)
    - Poetry Spots - Dub, Undated; ID: 128.0161 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0161)
    - Poetry Spots; Latin Empire B roll, 1990; ID: 128.0162 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0162)
    - Griffith Rough Cut & Paterson, Undated; ID: 128.0163 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0163)
    - Poetry Project: Helen Adam, 1996; ID: 128.0164 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0164)
    - Holman, Ginsberg, Jordan - only, Undated; ID: 128.0165 (Box 7, Media ID: 128.0165)
    - Poetry Spots I, Undated; ID: 128.0166 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0166)
    - Poetry Spots - Edit, Undated; ID: 128.0167 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0167)
    - Poetry Spots I: Cuts 5 & 6, Undated; ID: 128.0168 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0168)
    - Poetry Spots Season One, 1992; ID: 128.0169 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0169)
    - PoSpots Special Season One, Undated; ID: 128.0170 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0170)
    - [1] - Cut 1 Video Poetry Promos [2]-- Cut 2 Video Poetry Show, 1989; ID: 128.0171 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0171)
    - Poetry Spots [1]-- Compilation #1 [2]-- Compilation #2, 1992; ID: 128.0172A (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0172A)
    - Poetry Spots 2 - Selections, Undated; ID: 128.0173 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0173)
    - John Ash Poem: Vanishing Suspension, Undated; ID: 128.0174 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0174)
    - John Ash / Paul Beatty, Undated; ID: 128.0175 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0175)
    - Poetry Spots Season III, Undated; ID: 128.0176 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0176)
    - Poetry Spots Season III Compliation Reel, Undated; ID: 128.0177 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0177)
    - Poetry Spots Season III Compliation, Undated; ID: 128.0178 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0178)
    - Poetry Spots Season III - Spot Reel, Undated; ID: 128.0179 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0179)
    - Poetry Spots IV - Air Master, Undated; ID: 128.0180 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0180)
    - You Startin' Wif Me - A Tracie Morris Poetry Film Short, 1992; ID: 128.0181 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0181)